{
    "subject": "resource/Madame_Butterfly_(1915_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Mary_Pickford",
    "human_readable": "Mary Pickford stars in the 1915 film Madame Butterfly.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9668383002281189,
            "question": "What was the name of the film starring Mary Pickford in 1915?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9379923343658447,
            "question": "Who starred in the 1915 film Madame Butterfly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9344664216041565,
            "question": "What was Mary Pickford's role in Madame Butterfly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9040167927742004,
            "question": "In what year did Mary Pickford appear in Madame Butterfly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7138242125511169,
            "question": "What other films did Mary Pickford star in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5280987620353699,
            "question": "What type of film was Madame Butterfly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4515191912651062,
            "question": "How did Mary Pickford contribute to the history of cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44114238023757935,
            "question": "Was Madame Butterfly a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32747310400009155,
            "question": "Is Mary Pickford known for appearing in silent films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03882906585931778,
            "question": "Is there any connection between the film and the opera?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mary Pickford stars in the 1915 film Madame Butterfly.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6911_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mary Pickford known for appearing in silent films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6911_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Madame Butterfly a successful film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6911_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Mary Pickford contribute to the history of cinema?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6911_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6911_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that confirm Mary Pickford starred in the 1915 film \"Madame Butterfly.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}